[OVERDO]
[Episode 33]
[Tomb of Brother, Li Boze]
[Tomb of Cheng Army member, Murong Qingyu]
[Tomb of Martyr, Ye Zhihong]
When Boze sees Qingyu,
he'll definitely complain about me.
That's for sure.
All your lives,
you two always
competed for Qingyu's favor.
[Tomb of Brother, Li Boze]
I was never as childish as he was.
If...
If you had the chance...
you'd have tried to get closer to him,
to understand him.
Maybe you could've become true brothers.
I let Qingyu down.
I didn't take good care of Ms. Ye.
Ms. Ye didn't need your care.
She was the bravest and freest woman
I've ever met.
She and Boze...
both did what they thought was right.
So...
So we should do the same.
Susu,
leave Nancheng with Le'an.
When this is over,
I'll come get you.
I've entrusted Le'an to Hai Tangqing.
They're already in Beicheng.
I'm staying here
with you.
Susu...
Come with me.
Why are we here?
A couple shares the same bed in life
and the same grave in death.
In the future,
I think we should be buried here.
Ren Susu,
are you finally giving in?
After more than a decade
of going in circles,
I've long given in.
I wanted to give this to you a decade ago,
but you ran away.
I also wanted to give it to you
at the engagement party,
but you threw it away.
Now, I'm giving it to you.
What are you going
to do with it?
♪ I happened to ♪
♪ Hear your name ♪
I want to wear it.
♪ And all the memories ♪
♪ Came flooding back ♪
We live and die together,
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
never forsaking each other.
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
♪ My heart pounding ♪
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
♪ In the misty train car ♪
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
♪ If you have any ♪
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
[New East Asia Chamber of Commerce]
Zhang Mingshu, you piece of trash!
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
There was a situation,
but we salvaged a batch of drugs.
We can deploy it as planned today.
You sure about it?
Yes.
Today's the temple fair.
Many people will gather in Nancheng.
It's our prime opportunity.
Okay.
The Chamber of Commerce
will also proceed as planned.
I'm leaving this
entirely to you.
If you fail again,
Mr. Zhang,
you and your family will
all meet your deaths.
Understood.
You heard him.
If it doesn't work this time,
you will pay with your lives!
Yes!
Our people found out that
Zhang Mingshu's planning
to poison the entire city.
How many lives is this going to cost?
The chairman was killed,
and the pharmaceutical factory
was blown up.
For the Zhangs
to regain their masters' trust,
he'll stop at nothing.
[City God Temple]
For the poisoning initiation,
two places are most likely:
the most crowded place in Nancheng
or the place with the greatest influence.
[City God Temple]
The City God Temple's
holding a fair today,
so it's a very likely place.
There's another possibility.
[Water Plant]
The water plant?
If he gets his way,
we'll be doomed beyond redemption.
I'll go notify the police.
It's useless.
After the pharmaceutical factory
was blown up,
Zhang Mingshu destroyed
all the research data and documents
for the Red Pill.
Without evidence,
the police won't investigate.
Also, early this morning,
the East Asia Chamber of Commerce
officially protested to the government,
claiming that Ms. Ye's bombing
of the pharmaceutical factory
was disrupting
a legitimate private business.
They even rallied all the major
chambers of commerce.
The temple fair is imminent.
Principal, say no more.
Just give the order.
Everyone,
split into two groups.
One group will
follow me and Laiyi
to the water plant today.
The other group will follow me
to the temple fair.
I'll go with my sisters
to stop the poisoning.
How'd you get rid of the drugs?
Destroy them with fire.
I have an expert for that.
At the temple fair,
we mustn't disturb the crowd.
We cannot cause public panic,
lest accidents occur.
-Noted.
Everyone,
after this battle,
no one will know or sing our praises;
we may well sacrifice in silence
before the dawn.
If you regret it now,
you can leave.
I know
each of you has family waiting for you.
It's not shameful
to want out.
We're not leaving.
I heard this year's temple fair
is especially lively.
When all this is over,
let's go join in the fun.
Okay.
Then it's a deal.
I'll see you at the City God Temple's
butterfly crisp stand.
Okay,
it's a deal.
[Dongjiadu Water Plant]
What's going on?
Someone's attacking the water plant!
Run!
Master ordered that
no one must be left alive!
Principal, there are too many of them!
Laiyi, cover me!
Be careful.
Mom, I'm so thirsty.
I want some water.
Thirsty?
Come, Iet's go get some water.
Yay! There's water!
Leave!
Go, go!
Not this way!
Leave!
Go!
Take her out!
Go up and help them now.
Susu!
-Come out!
Watch out, Young Master Qingyi!
Laiyi!
Laiyi.
This time,
I did pretty well, huh?
You lied to me again!
Go run 20 laps.
This isn't the aviation school.
There's no track.
Isn't this hospital big enough
for you to run?
I don't have time to run.
I have to help you find your ring.
Aren't you
a lucky one
to have such a considerate
subordinate like me?
Does this look like me?
It's easy to draw the form
but not the spirit.
[Me]
This captures your spirit.
If I'd known earlier,
I would've just let you rot in the river!
You finally admit it.
You're the one who
force-fed me opium.
You're also the one who
caused the explosion.
So what if it was me?
At this point,
I have nothing to hide.
To bring down the Murongs and the Lis,
our Zhang family has
put years of painstaking effort
into plotting everything.
[Nancheng Station]
Back then,
we Zhangs
planned the North-South Railway explosion
just to make the Murongs and the Lis
turn against each other.
But you
actually found out about it.
Don't you think you deserve to die?
Help!
There's a man in the water!
Someone save him!
But you were lucky
and were saved.
[18 Songbin Lane]
After you went missing,
Li Rongzhang suspected
that we Zhangs did it.
To prevent him from finding any clues,
I had to eradicate the root.
Because the Murong and Li babies
were swapped at birth,
Li Rongzhang always refused to
make an enemy of the Murongs.
I could only drag him down,
to share the profits with me.
Who knew that this matter
would be discovered by Murong Qingyu?
So I killed Huo Zongqi
and framed Ren Susu
to make you brothers
turn against each other.
[Marriage Notice:
Murong Qingyu & Fang Mulan]
And on the eve of Murong Qingyu's wedding,
I instigated Huo Minxian...
to disrupt the wedding.
I didn't expect him to really die.
Now,
no one can stop me.
I will
have the last laugh!
As long as
I pour this into the pipe,
everyone in Nancheng
will have to pave the way for me!
Go to hell!
Susu, how are you?
I'm fine.
The priority is
to get rid of the drugs quickly.
Tasia.
You're injured?
I'm fine.
Proceed with the plan.
Okay.
Will this really work?
I'm a professional
when it comes to handling gunpowder.
We'll shoot the drugs up into the sky
with the fireworks
and burn them to ashes.
Fireworks reach temperatures
of over 1,000 degrees when they explode.
Earlier, Godfather and Ms. Ye
proved with their lives that
high temperatures are the best way
to destroy this drug.
There are citizens
all over outside right now.
If we get into a fight
with the Zhangs
and the drugs accidentally leak,
the innocent will inevitably get hurt.
So destroying it on the spot
is the best solution.
Put it in.
Murong Qingyi,
what about Ren Susu?
If you leave now,
you can still live to see her.
Otherwise...
you'll die here with me.
Think about it.
Is it worth throwing your life away
for those irrelevant people?
Those who were persecuted by you
and lost their lives,
are they irrelevant people too?
This punch
is for Laiyi.
is for Boze.
This last punch...
is for my elder brother!
♪ This spark of wildfire
spreading across the plains ♪
♪ Stirs embers that refuse to fade ♪
♪ I seize fate by the hand ♪
♪ Accusing it of refusing to relent ♪
♪ Pain and joy blur before my eyes ♪
♪ Fate keeps replaying its endless cycle ♪
♪ The love that refused to die ♪
This is spectacular!
♪ Has already consumed us both ♪
Qingyi,
do you see this?
We've succeeded.
Qingyu...
Boze...
Father...
Ms. Ye...
Laiyi...
Let these brilliant fireworks...
pay tribute to your loyal souls.
[Butterfly Crisp]
Was anyone waiting around here just now?
No.
Come and take a look!
Miss.
Are you Ren Susu?
A man asked me to give this to you.
Where is he?
He gave me a few silver dollars
early in the morning
and told me to wait for you at the
City God Temple's butterfly crisp stand.
I don't know where he is either.
He said he's leaving for a while to do
something very important,
and that you should take care of yourself.
Qingyi.
Qingyi,
stand up.
Hurry now.
Stand up!
You brat,
what are you waiting for?
Susu and Le'an are waiting for you.
Susu,
passing through the raging fire,
we become sparks,
not the ashes.
If this time
I don't return,
you must live well.
Live for yourself.
In the past,
it was always me waiting for you.
This time,
it's your turn to wait for me.
Okay?
Okay.
This time...
I'll wait for you.
Susu.
Waiting is torturous,
but it also carries hope.
You have a long life ahead.
This might be
the last thing I can do for you.
I often wonder:
if we could return to that second
and start all over again...
what kind of life would we've lived?
There must be such a universe.
Qingyu and Ms. Ye
will tie the knot
and spread their wings freely.
Congratulations!
Boze and Hai Tangqing
will be in perfect harmony,
two hearts beating as one.
And the frozen soil in Mother's heart
will be melted by her own spring.
She'll finally use her unconsumed love
to illuminate each of us equally.
Hands off! It's mine!
Don't mess things up for me!
Susu,
let me take you somewhere.
[27 Liuli Alley, East District]
And we will
meet in the first snow of Beicheng.
I'll be a doctor,
and you'll be a painter.
♪ I happened to ♪
♪ Hear your name ♪
We might argue over
♪ And all the memories ♪
the unwatered gentian flowers
♪ Came flooding back ♪
and the uncleaned swing.
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
Then, we'll
make up because of
the smell of braised pork in the kitchen.
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
♪ My heart pounding ♪
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
♪ In the misty train car ♪
You'll smile at me,
with a butterfly crisp in your hands.
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
This time,
♪ If you have any ♪
we can afford to
waste our lives in such trivial ways.
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
♪ Memories are like falling into a trap ♪
♪ Full of mud ♪
♪ The more I struggle,
the more suffocated I become ♪
We made it!
♪ But I couldn't resist collecting them ♪
Come on, get on.
♪ I keep collecting ♪
♪ Every word and comment ♪
♪ They speak of you ♪
♪ You're becoming clear ♪
♪ So far yet so clear ♪
♪ Ever since forgetting you ♪
♪ Became second nature ♪
You're squeezing my hand.
♪ I still can't erase ♪
Afraid I'll get lost again?
♪ Completely erase ♪
What do you mean "again"?
♪ The certainty of my hand in yours ♪
Maybe we really
♪ You are so clear ♪
once got separated.
♪ So close and so clear ♪
It's okay.
Even if we get separated this second,
♪ If you possibly ♪
in the next,
I will find you.
♪ Still have the courage ♪
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
Where are we going?
♪ Please stop doubting ♪
♪ My determination to run away with you ♪
To the place where my heart
started beating for you again.
♪ Time has a way of smoothing away ♪
♪ The past ♪
♪ The past that had you ♪
♪ I pretend not to remember you ♪
♪ If I really can't remember you ♪
♪ I'll start loving you all over again ♪
♪ From the day I forget you ♪
♪ You are so clear ♪
♪ So close and so clear ♪
♪ If you possibly ♪
♪ Still have the courage ♪
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
♪ Please stop doubting ♪
♪ My determination to run away with you ♪
♪ Having loved you deeply ♪
♪ Was the best decision I've made ♪
[From Nancheng to Beicheng]
[The End]